NASHEET JAMAL

Address: Marjan Island Resort & Spa, managed by

AccorHotels, Ras al Khaimah

Mob: +971526364234

Skype: nasheet.jamal

UAE Driving licence no: 198788

Email: nasheet_jamal@yahoo.co.in

Age: 33

Nationality: Indian

Marital status: Married



SUMMARY

A multi-skilled IT professional with good all-round supervisory and technical expertise. Very capable with a proven ability to ensure the smooth running of information and communications technology systems and to provide IT services that will improve the efficiency and performance of a company. Extensive practical knowledge of complex systems builds, hardware and software testing, network support, technical support and computer repairs.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

10/2019 - Pre-Opening IT Task Force Pullman Sharjah AccorHotels.

5 Star Hotel, 180 rooms 3 outlets 10 meeting rooms and 1 ballroom up to 200



06/2013 - Present (8year)

MARJAN ISLAND RESORT & SPA - Managed by AccorHotels, Ras al Khaimah, UAE

Part of Pre-Opening Team



5 star hotel, 299 rooms, 157 residences, 11 outlets, 3 meeting rooms + ballroom up to 300.

Acting IT Manager (IT Supervisor) – November 2015 – Present Reporting to: General Manager – Regional IT Director Middle East

Achievements so far:

- Successfully switched/linked independent network to AccorHotels IT centralised system.
- Kept a safe and secure work environment; developing personal growth opportunities.
- Maintained quality service to both guests and employees by establishing and enforcing organization standards.
- PCI DSS implementation

Responsible for my previous tasks as IT supervisor plus:

- Day-to-day support of IT systems for business systems, office systems, computer networks, and telephony systems throughout the hotel. Support to deliver an excellent Guest and Member experience.
- Maintains information technology strategies by managing staff; researching and implementing technological strategic solutions.
- Accomplishes information technology staff results by communicating job expectations; planning, monitoring, initiating, coordinating, and enforcing systems, policies, and procedures.
- Directs technological research by studying organization goals, strategies, practices, and user projects.
- Recommends information technology strategies, policies, and procedures by evaluating organization outcomes; identifying problems; evaluating trends; anticipating requirements.
- Assisting in accomplishes financial objectives by forecasting requirements; preparing an annual budget; scheduling expenditures; analysing variances; initiating corrective action.
- Maintains professional and technical knowledge by attending educational workshops; reviewing professional publications; establishing personal networks.

IT Supervisor – November 2014 - November 2015 (1 year)

Reporting to: IT Manager

- Network, security & troubleshooting
- Opera PMS, Micros Point of Sale System (POS)
- Handling the Hotel Guest Internet, Wi-Fi Related Issues.
- Guest Room IPTV Issues.
- Offices Troubleshooting.
- Front Office & Back Offices troubleshooting.
- Concierge desk troubleshooting.
- Networking for the Meetings.
- Micros 3700 (Point of sales).
- Staff Internet
- Tiger TMS (Guest Wi-Fi).
- Air Angel (Guest Wi-Fi Cloud based)
- Opera Related.
- Update the Details of the IT Department.
- Wi-Fi Router Access Point Configuration.
- Desktop, Laptop, Printer, Scanner troubleshooting.
- FMC (Oracle based)
- FBM

CCTV Security Agent / IT Clerk- June 2013 - November 2014 (5 m)

Reporting to: Executive Assistant Manager

Controlling CCTV System

12/2012 - 05/2013 (6months) DigiWorld India

IT Support Help Desk - December 2012 - May 2013 (6m)

Reporting to: Owner

- Networking & Printer
- Workstation & Laptop troubleshooting



- Installation Windows Vista, Xp, windows 7.
- Anti-virus Installation

<u>04/2012 – 11/2012 (7months) Indira Gandhi International</u> <u>Airport</u>



Customer Service Associate – April 2012 – November 2012 (7m)

Reporting to: Customer Service Senior Supervisor

- Check In desk support
- Ground handling
- Guest help desk support

10/2010 - 03/2012 (17 months) Cogent E Services Private Limited



Customer Service Associate – October 2010 – March 2012 (17m)

Reporting to: Customer Service Senior Supervisor Support Airtel mobile & broadband landline services. Airtel C.C.E (Customer care executive) in Domestic B.P.O India.

- Domestic Airtel mobile network service provider call centre
- Internet Broadband landline as cashier
- More than 4 state covering on call support

IT RELATED SKILLS

- Networking & Printer, workstation troubleshooting.
- Opera PMS, Admin skills.
- Micros 3700 Point of Sale System.
- Back Of House Systems: SUN, FBM, Paytrax (Payroll & HR System), NEC PABX, Tiger HSIA System.
- Air Angel (Guest Wi-Fi Cloud based)

AWARDS

 MARJAN ISLAND RESORT AND SPA – Managed by ACCORHOTELS Employee of the month June 2015

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

- Graduate Bachelor of business administration (B.B.A.) From Jamia Hamdard, New Delhi (2007-2011)
- Intermediate passed from U.P board (2006-07)
- High school from N.I.O.S. (2003-04)

OTHER COURSES & TRAININGS

- Hardware, Networking & Security System from IACM Institute India.
- Diploma in Graphic Designing from The Professional institute India.
- AccorHotels corporate trainings

Reference:-

Name: - Mr. Guillermo Carlos Salvatori Currently: - Hotel Manager Movenpick JLT Dubai.

Previous: -EAM/ F&B Manager at Marjan Island Resort and Spa Managed By Accor Hotels RAK.

Contact Number: - +971567608921

Name: - Ahmed Soliman

Currently: - Residence Manager at Marjan Island Resort and Spa Managed By Accor Hotels RAK

Previous: - General Manager City Hotel RAK

Contact Number: - +971507790248

Name: - Mohanad Al Ali

Currently: - Cluster Director of Sales & Marketing Manazil Group

Contact Number: - +971502775144